<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
  <rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>KetogenicFamily.com</title>
    <link>https://ketogenicfamily.com</link>
    <description>KetogenicFamily.com - Follow our progress towards a permanent ketogenic lifestyle</description>
    <item>
      <title>I am a lean person, why I quit a 5 day fast after only 4 days</title>
      <link>https://ketogenicfamily.com/blog/post/2017_10_20-why-i-quit-fasting-after-only-4-days</link>
      <description>What I learned attempting a prolonged fast as a lean person</description>
    </item> <item>
      <title>Why we chose a ketogenic lifestyle</title>
      <link>https://ketogenicfamily.com/blog/post/2017_10_26-why-we-chose-ketogenic-lifestyle</link>
      <description>For years we struggled with low fat, high carb diets... until we discovered keto, and we've never looked back...</description>
    </item> <item>
      <title>What is the ketogenic diet?</title>
      <link>https://ketogenicfamily.com/blog/post/2017_11_06-what-is-the-ketogenic-diet</link>
      <description>The ketogenic diet is a low carb, high fat diet designed to train your body to use fat for energy, break your sugar addiction and help you lose weight naturally</description>
    </item> <item>
      <title>What role is food playing in my overall health and wellbeing?</title>
      <link>https://ketogenicfamily.com/blog/post/2017_11_12-what-role-is-food-playing-in-health-and-wellbeing</link>
      <description>Your body is a complex organic machine with many moving parts.  Everything you consume, dietary food and drink, has a direct effect on your health.</description>
    </item> <item>
      <title>Should you exercise when starting the ketogenic diet?</title>
      <link>https://ketogenicfamily.com/blog/post/2017_11_25-should-you-exercise-when-starting-ketogenic-diet</link>
      <description>Exercising can be difficult for people when starting keto, because of the effects of the keto flu.  When starting keto, you may consider taking a break from exercising or exercising with a friend for safety and to avoid injury.</description>
    </item> <item>
      <title>What is the role of fasting on the ketogenic diet?</title>
      <link>https://ketogenicfamily.com/blog/post/2017_12_02-what-is-role-of-fasting-on-ketogenic-diet</link>
      <description>Fasting, when refraining from eating food and only drinking water for between 16 hours to several days, is a means of accelerating weight loss, and boosting ketone levels.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
  </rss>